Woke up this morning, the world was gray Didn't
know the colors had all faded away Been living in
a room with the curtains drawn tight Then you
flipped a switch and turned on the light Oh, oh
I'm seeing an electric color Finding a rhythm I
never knew Dancing in a brand new summer My whole
world feels bright and new It's an electric
color feeling And it all started with you
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh Yeah
The city sounds were just a buzz in my ear A static
station I could never quite hear But now the
noise is turning into a song And I finally feel
like I belong I'm seeing an electric color
Finding a rhythm I never knew Dancing in a brand
new summer My whole world feels bright anew It's
an electric color feeling And it all started
with you
The beat is getting stronger I can't hide it any
longer My heart is playing catch up to the music
Turning way
up
Shh, shh.
I'm seeing an electric color Finding a rhythm I
never knew Dancing in a brand new summer My whole
world feels bright anew It's an electric color
feeling And it all started with you Electric
color
It's all because of you